(Sheldon:)I'll walk you through it.
(Sheldon:)The game is not called
"Words With Strangers."
No. It is not even called
"Words With Acquaintances."
It is called "Words With..."
(Raj:)I'm not finishing your sentence.
You pulled the plug on my funk.
"Friends." It's "Words With Friends."
Which Stephen Hawking and I officially are.
(Sheldon:)Now all I need is a bunk bed with a slide.
(Sheldon:)I'll have everything I've ever wanted
since I was 6 years old.
That's really nice. I'm happy for you.
(Sheldon:)And I'm happy for you too.
(Sheldon:)You are now friends with someone who
is officially friends with Stephen Hawking.
(Sheldon:)Enjoy it, boys. You may have peaked.
(Howard:)I know Stephen Hawking. I worked with him.
Yeah, and if they ever come out
with a game called...
..."Words With People You Once
Worked With," you'll be off to the races.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I don't think
this actually means that...
(Sheldon:)Hold that thought.
Professor Hawking has made a move.
(Sheldon:)Boy, oh, boy.
(Sheldon:)It's only a matter of time
before we're coming up...
(Sheldon:)...with fun nicknames for each other.
I'll be Coop. Yeah. He'll be Wheels.
(Sheldon:)If he's okay with that.
(Raj(putting game back on and removing shirt):)All right.
(Raj(putting game back on and removing shirt):)Crank up the a.c., boys.
It's gonna get hot in here.
Young man, young man
Get yourself off the ground